good evening ladies and gentlemen and
welcome
to the 20th foundation day celebrations
of icici prudential life
i'm xenia fernandez and i will be your
host for this
grand evening so foundation day each
year
has been about getting together it's
about celebrating like a
big family this year also we are
celebrating this day with the same
spirit
when we're all connected virtually i
know for sure
that you're all in this festive mode and
you have the same energy
and enthusiasm around you know some of
our awardees today
they've also shared pictures where they
have recreated the magic of foundation
day
in the cozy corners of their homes with
goodies that were part
of the gift hamper that was sent to them
before today's event
wow wasn't that spectacular
you know this is what defines us this
passion
and our love for the organization and
what was amazing to see
was to see all of our awardees with
their strongest pillars of strength
their family members
celebrating along with them you know it
is said that with the support of a
family
one can win a losing battle but without
the family's support even a winning
battle
is lost come rain come shine
your family will always be there for you
to cheer you on
and it's due to all of them that you are
here
with us today so ladies and gentlemen
let's applaud for
our families
it's now time to get to the moment we
have all
been waiting for yes ladies and
gentlemen
it is time to open with the awards
[Music]
many many congratulations once again to
all the awardees and big congratulations
to their family members you know there
are few pursuits that are nobler than
the pursuit of service to the motherland
it is truly about placing institution
before self
withstanding unimaginable challenges
and also having a never say die
attitude it offers much to learn from
and we are so fortunate to have with us
today
one such person who has that rich
experience from serving in the forces
but also has the additional perspective
of being a corporate leader ladies and
gentlemen
please join me in welcoming captain
raghu rahman thank you i mean
after your glowing accolades even i am
curious to hear what i'm going to say
thank you captain that was
what other than truly inspiring i must
say
you know it is truly stories like these
that remind us of the true worth of life
all of you too protect the future of
your customers families
you help protect lives i'm sure the
learnings that sir has shared with us
today
will really resonate with us and we will
carry them back to our work and indeed
as life lessons for ourselves so captain
thank you once again so ladies and
gentlemen
it's time for some brain teasing
yes it's trivia time i have a few
questions for all of you
just like kbc just like you know fastest
finger
first whoever answers first
will be the winner okay or it
but we also have a surprise gift for the
winners
and the winner names will be announced
towards the end of the show so stay
tuned
okay pull up your sleeves and get
ready to answer the questions remember
the fastest one wins
type the answer mention your employee id
and send it to us because we have some
goodies to win
so are you ready i need a virtual yes
i can feel you okay oh you are ready
okay let's go with question number one
do we have background score guys kidding
okay here we go
in which year did icici prudential life
become the first private life insurer to
attain
assets under management of 1 trillion
in which fiscal year and your options
are fiscal year 2015
option b fiscal year 2017
and option c fiscal year 2016.
oh guess what that's not all we have
question number three
so if you've not got the first two don't
worry i have you covered
okay as long as you are ready
here comes the full and final question
of the quiz
ladies and gentlemen brace yourselves
for question number three type in your
answer quickly
send it to us thank you everybody for
participating
so wholeheartedly that it just feels
amazing you know it transports me back
to the live foundation day that we had
but actually i don't miss it anymore
because i can
feel your energy you know talent is
god's gift to us
what we do with our talent is a gift
back
from us to god the upcoming performance
tonight
celebrates the very sense of this
beautiful gift he is the winner
of indian idol season 5 and a star
performer
he is a bollywood playback singer and he
is known for his hit song
he actually sings in nine different
languages and
he has so far sung more than 500
songs in playback ladies and gentlemen
no prizes for guessing who this is
please put your hands together for the
rock star
the performer the entertainer and the
all-rounder shri ramachandran
these two decades of our journey would
not have been possible
without all of you while the show may
end here
please do not end the celebrations at
your home
it is your special day so please enjoy
the evening with your loved ones
your loved ones who have shared your
highs
your lows and given you the strength to
work each and every day ladies and
gentlemen
enjoy and celebrate this spirit of
togetherness
this is me zenia fernandez signing off
have a great evening
thank you good night god bless and may
you
and your loved ones keep healthy and
keep safe